总有人问我 "谁是roger furlong?"
People are always asking me, "Who is roger furlong?"
我经常推荐他们去看一本好书里的某一段落
And I always refer them to the same passage of the good book.
圣经
The scriptures.
"饮水即知挖井人"
"Wherefore by their fruits ye shall know them."
好 我们开始
All right, let's do it.
作为第一女儿 我身上责任重大
Being the first daughter is a big responsibility.
很好 但我很乐意为国家效力
Good. But I'm happy to serve my country
并帮助我妈妈 很不错 嗯
And to help out my mom. That's very good, yes.
我爱你 妈妈 哦 不 亲爱的
I love you, mom. Oh, no, honey.
你需要表现的很诚恳 亲爱的
You've got to say it like you mean it, though, darling.
多简单 就像"我爱你 妈妈
It's so easy. It's like, "I love you, mom.
我爱你"呃 不是那样
I love you." Well, not like that.
我的国家和我的生活
There are great changes
都会发生了很大的变化
coming for this nation and my own life, too.
去年我遇到一个叫Jason的男孩
Last year I met a boy called jason.
我不清楚 她该说男孩还是男人?
Mm, I don't know, should she say boy or man?
-如果要更清楚的话? -对 这问题提得好 夫人
Just to be clear? Yes, that's a good question, ma'am.
我当然是男人 不是吗?
It's clear that I'm a man, isn't it?
我都好几年买酒不查驾照了了 大概三年了吧
I haven't been carded for years. Like, three years.
我只是 不知道效果会不会很好
I just-- I don't know if this is gonna play well.
你知道不? 我也有这种感觉
You know what? I started to feel that way myself.
这是个大会 大家都喜欢这种狗屁
It's a convention. People love this shit.
怎么会不好? 我们在恋爱
How could it not play well? We're in love.
-是 应该会很好 -可以的
Yeah, it might play well. It could.
-很有可能的 -嗯嗯
I think it might. Mm-hmm.
我受不了Karen了
I cannot take karen anymore.
都好几周了 她连一个陈述句都没说过
It's been weeks and she has yet to speak a declarative sentence.
律师都喜欢掩盖他们的立场
Lawyers tend to cover their bases.
我那次车祸时深有体会
I know that from my car accident.
当时和一个律师撞了
With a lawyer.
我就直接把她消音
I just tune her out.
知道不 像住在高速公路旁一样
You know, like living next to a highway.
去年我认识了个小伙子叫Jason 之后我们相爱了
Last year I met a guy called jason and we fell in love.
好吧 宝贝
All right, sweetheart,
听起来你不像是恋爱中的人儿
it doesn't sound like you're in love to me.
更像是被塔利班绑架了
It sounds like you've been kidnapped by the taliban.
没错 我们即将结婚
Exactly. And we're going to get married.
所以我想把Jason介绍给你们
So I'd like to introduce you to jason.
出来吧 亲爱的
Come on out, honey.
你听起来像生气了 我就是生气了!
It sounds like you're angry. I am angry!
好吧 这就是你为啥听起来像生气了
Well, that's why you sound like you're angry.
隐藏起来 掩饰一会
Hide it. Conceal it for a second.
说得好 掩饰住
Good, conceal it.
如果你在北美大陆任何一个地方吃西葫芦
If you eat a zucchini anywhere in mainland north america,
有20%几率你吃到的是我的西葫芦
There's a 20% chance it's one of my zucchini.
嗯 我是西葫芦的脑残粉
Well, I am such a zucchini fan,
我甚至能进行光合作用
I practically photosynthesize.
明年这个几率要达到24%
next year I want 24%.
呃 听着 这位dan先生
Well, listen, dan here is the man.
是白宫那边来的新人
He's fresh from the white house,
他有不计其数的
He's got a rolodex as crammed
和人体藏毒者的粪兜一样多的人脉
As a drug mule's poop pocket.
而且我要把西葫芦提升一个档次
And I want to take zucchini to the next level.
好 明天之前我在城里
Great, I'm in town till tomorrow,
今天有什么大人物能让我见见吗?
So any big dogs you can get me in a room with today?
这有点棘手
That's gonna be tricky.
大家都出城去开大会了
Everyone's out of town for the convention,
留在特区的只有连锁药店的人而已 但--
So the only people left in dc work at cvs, but--
dan只是谦虚罢了 你认识所有人 对吧 dan？
Dan's just being modest. I mean, you know everybody, right, dan?
翻翻你的名片盒吧 哥们
Flex that rolodex, pal.
呃 好
Uh, yeah.
你听说过jonah ryan吗?
You ever hear of jonah ryan?
-没听过 -我的老哥们 认识很久了
No. Old buddy of mine. We go way back.
爱死他了 我今天能让你和他见面
Love that guy. I can get you in a room with him today.
好 听着 不谈生意了 吃饭吧
All right, listen. Enough business, let's eat.
好吗? 但不吃西葫芦 怎样?
Okay? But probably not fucking zucchini, right?
我想为把Jason介绍给你们
I'd like to introduce you to jason.
出来 亲爱的
Come on out, honey.
好 现在亲一个
Okay, and now a kiss.
-哦！还得下点功夫 -不止一点功夫
Oh! That needs work. That needs work.
-哪里? -全部
Which part? All of it.
-亲别人一下是有多难?-就是说啊
How hard is it to kiss somebody? I know.
你就把头靠近一人
You just put your head close to theirs,
嘴唇贴一起就行了 对吧?
you let your lips touch, you know?
这还需要我示范吗?
Do I need to demonstrate this?
-不需要 -不需要嘛
No. No.
好了 他可以自己练习出场
Okay, he can practice the walk on his own time.
我们现在真得核对一下总统的演讲词了
We really need to look at the president's speech now.
这是人类的情感 你不能着急
Hey, human emotion, you can't rush it.
又不是精确的科学 Amy
It's not a precise science, amy.
所有科学都是精确的 这就是科学的意义
All sciences are precise. That's what science means.
这是见仁见智的话题
That's open to interpretation.
对 说得好
Yes. Extraordinary.
夫人 路易安那州有个死刑犯
Ma'am, there's a death row inmate in louisiana.
呃 真不错
Ugh, sounds good.
他死刑使用了新型的复合毒药
He was given a new drug cocktail,
但不管用 所以基本上他没死
But it didn't work, so basically he's not dead.
-半死不活 -半死不活?
He's half dead. Half dead?
-是 他的死刑被执行了一半 -真可怕
Yeah, he's been half-acuted. Awful.
就像是头被砍掉了但没死
Like being decapitated but surviving.
杀鸡时很常见
Happens to chickens a lot.
呃 有人会说
Well, some might say that
我们才是一群没脑袋的人(缺乏领导)
we're being slightly headless ourselves.
我们应该专注于你的演讲词
We really need to focus on your speech.
嗯 现在新出的这个死刑的事 应该优先考虑
Well, there is this new execution issue, so that's the priority.
好 我们是不是该发表一份声明或...
Right. Do you think we should issue a statement or...
是 但得是一份如果事情有变就可以调整的声明
Yes, but a statement that can be repurposed if things change.
他死了的声明 没死的声明 或不知死没死的声明
He dies, he doesn't die, or whatever.
对 很机智 谢谢 谢谢
Yeah, that's very clever. Thank you. Thank you.
所以说这是真的
So it's true.
他们黑了成千上百死亡孩童的数据
They hacked the data of thousands of dead kids
以那些丧子的父母为目标 发放这个煽情的宣传单
To directly target bereaved parents with this charming mailer.
哇哦 死孩子-- 从来就不是什么好事
Wow, dead kids-- that never sounds good
除非你是个压力山大的单身妈妈
Unless you're a stressed-out single mom.
出了这事 他们还对我进行民调反对我? 真是够了 我退出
This and they polled against me? That's it, I'm out.
不行 先生 这步棋走错了 你不能--
No, sir, that's the wrong move. You can't--
我只接受一个小矮子告诉我该做什么
There's only one midget I'm gonna let tell me what to do,
而我现在就去告诉她我受够了
And I'm gonna go tell her that I'm done.
她没时间找人来接你的班
She doesn't have time to replace you.
她要怎么做 给Gary装个丁丁 让他干这个工作吗?
What's she gonna do, pin a dick on gary and give him the job?
她有好几个小时的时间呢
She's got a couple hours.
我是说 在政治里 这时间已经绰绰有余了
I mean, that's more than enough time in politics.
不 等等 并不够 真糟糕哦
No, wait a minute, it's not. Tough shitski.
那么我想对所有年轻人说
so I'd like to say to all you young people,
加入我吧
Join me
让我们一起撼动全美
And let's rock these united states.
所以 确实 我们想一步一步来
So, really, we wanted to go progressive.
- 夫人 - 啥事?
- Ma'am. - Yeah?
对手阵营里有个我的大学同学 能派的上用场
I have a useful college friend in the enemy camp
没什么脑子 还管不住嘴
With a small brain and a big mouth.
她说Obrien参议员的竞选搭档
She says that senator o'brien's running mate
会是Laura Montez
Is going to be laura montez.
- Montez? - 是的
- Montez? - Yeah.
是那个新上任的墨西哥参议员Laura Montez?
New mexico senator laura montez?
- 嗯哼 - 她很聪明
Mm-hmm. She's brilliant.
很漂亮 又迷人
She's pretty. She's charming.
还是个女人!
She's a woman!
还他妈是少数民族的!
She's fucking ethnic!
这就是拉丁必杀技
This is latina geddon.
我倒希望我是那个在死囚室的人
I wish I was that guy on death row.
他可是连黑胆水都吐出来了啊
Apparently he's vomiting black bile.
- 好吧 我才不在乎 - 这步棋走的太大胆了
- Well, I don't even care. - This is such a bold move.
对手很聪明 这步棋走的确实挺大胆
It's clever. It's a really bold move.
- 是啊 我刚刚就是这么说的 - 好吧
- Yes, that's what I said. - All right.
网上没啥关于Montez的消息可挖
There's nothing on the internet about montez
除了明显用毁图秀秀合成的裸照也没啥东西
Except for the usual photoshopped nudity.
Obrien这次真的难倒我们了
O'brien's really broken us here.
他找了个性感的墨西哥女郎 你们再看看我的人?
He gets sexy mexi. What am I stuck with?
- Doyle? - 白头笑星的无趣老哥哥
- Doyle? - Steve martin's boring older brother.
我是说 现在说这个没什么意义
I mean, it doesn't make any sense to say this,
但是 我真的真的希望摆脱Doyle
But, I mean, I really, really wish we could get rid of doyle.
- 夫人 - 我们要是能把Danny Chung拉到我们这边儿多好?
- Ma'am.-  What if we could put danny chung on the ticket with us?
这样就能干掉他们这场南美狂欢节了 不是吗?
That would totally fuck up that fiesta of theirs, wouldn't it?
夫人 副总统来了 他看起来挺生气
Ma'am, the vice president's here and he looks pissed.
- 比平时更严重 - 你来啦 Andrew
- Even more than usual. - Hi, andrew.
女士 我们必须得单独谈谈
Ma'am, we need to have one of those one-on-one conversations.
- 啊哈 - 你懂得 就是你答应了
- Uh-huh. - You know, the kind that you promised
- 我们每周进行一次的那种 - 噢 咄咄逼人哟
- We'd have once a week. Oh, snarky.
好吧 那我们去卧室谈
Okay, yeah. Let's go have a talk in the bedroom.
房间里实在是很脏乱差 你真的不用我先帮你整整--
It's really dirty in there. Do you want me to tidy up just--
哦 我才不在乎 去他的吧
Oh, I don't care. Oh, fuck it.
噢 真抱歉 这里跟炸过似的
Oh, sorry for all this crap everywhere.
- 那么 什么--  - 听我说 Selina
- So, what's--  - hear me out, selina.
我很遗憾地通知你 我要退出竞选了
I regret to inform you that I'm stepping off the ticket.
- 啥? - 整个开幕式我会依然行使副总统的职责
What? I will stay on as veep through the inauguration.
然后我就坐上我的道奇车
Then I am getting in my Dodge
再也不管这堆破事儿了
dodge and I'm getting the hell out of dodge.
我不-- 我是说 你说的都是些啥啊--
I don't-- I mean, what are you talk--
我要气炸了 Ben
I am furious. Ben.
- 咋了? - 你听到他刚说的了吗?
- Yeah? - Are you hearing what I just heard?
我不确定是不是听错了
I don't know if I heard correctly.
- 要辞职? - 是这样 他要退出竞选
- Something about resigning? - Yeah, he's stepping off the ticket.
这是出于原则性考虑
It's a matter of principle.
我亲娘的七舅老爷啊
There is no way on god's green cock
你可不能因为原则就退出
That you can get out on matter of principle.
- 是啊 - 你只能说是因为健康状况
- That's right. - It has to be a health issue.
不 我无比健康
No, I'm perfectly healthy.
- 你有前列腺问题 - 我才不会这么说
- You have prostate problems. - I'm not gonna say that.
- 太尴尬了 - 那确实 这样才更真实
- That's embarrassing. - Exactly. That's what makes it more real.
我不会撒谎的 Selina
I'm not gonna lie, selina.
他说他不会撒谎的 Ben
He said he's not gonna lie, ben.
你造吗 副总统办公室那边
You know, there's been some very serious allegations
传出了很严重的性虐指控
Coming from the vice president's office about sexual abuse.
- 再说一遍? - 纳尼?
- Excuse me? - What?
- 是的 Jonah Ryan - Jonah? 额滴神啊
- Yeah, jonah ryan. - Jonah? Oh, my god.
可怜的实习生
Those poor interns.
不不不 Jonah是受害者
No, no, no, jonah's the victim.
- 性虐的是你的人Teddy - 纳尼?
- Your man teddy. - What?
是的 他爱抚Jonah蛋蛋的样子
Yeah, he's been fondling jonah's balls
就像是探囊寻宝似得
Like he's trying to figure out what the prize inside is.
我可是一点儿都不知情 Ben 啥都不知道 Selina
I knew nothing about this, ben. Nothing, selina.
- 所以你还怎么做个有原则的人呢... - 是啊
So how can you be a man of principle... Yeah.
-...如果你容忍了性虐这种事... - 性虐啊
-...When you're condoning sexual abuse... - Sexual abuse.
-...发生在你的办公室里? 你算什么人 教皇? - 在你办公室里啊
- ...In your own office? Who are you, the pope? - In your office.
我去写个草稿 来吧
i'll go write a draft. Come on.
是啊 前列腺问题 不是什么原则 对吧?
Yeah, prostate, not principle, huh?
是啊 我们会-- 我们会挺过去的
Yeah, that's what we'll-- we'll go with that.
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
噢天哪 杂么啦?
oh, my god, what's wrong?
- Doyle滚蛋了 - 你说啥?
- Doyle is a goner. - What?
他要退出竞选
He's stepping off the ticket.
纳尼? 竞选大会开到一半儿要退出?
What? In the middle of a convention?
- 我造! - 我们就找Chung来干掉Montez这个小婊砸
- I know! - Chung is our answer to montez.
- 他就是我们的少数民族代表 - 是酱!
- He can be our minority retort. - Yes!
嘿 性虐这招太好用了
Hey, way to work that sexual abuse.
简直比过年还高兴
it's like christmas except happy.
夫人 我很高兴 这是个好消息
Ma'am, I'm elated. This is great news.
是啊 你高兴的时候就是这表情
Yeah, that's your elated face.
我们得选个竞选伙伴了 好吗?
We need to pick a running mate now, okay?
你想讨论下我们有谁可选吗?
So do you want to discuss our options?
必须得是Danny Chung
It has to be danny chung.
我刚想这么说
That's exactly what I was gonna say.
对吧? 告诉他们 你是怎么回答的
Right? And tell what you just did.
好吧 我说
Well, I said,
"总统女士 非常遗憾..."
"Madam president, it is with deep regret..."
虚晃一枪 让她中计
Ah, false expectation. Set her up.
不 不 不 我说 "非常遗憾--
No, no, no. I said, "It is with deep regret--
恐怕我要接受您的邀请了"
I'm afraid I'm going to have to accept."
哇哦! 难以置信
oh! I can't believe it.
干得漂亮 非常漂亮
Nicely done. Very nicely done.
真是受不了他  什么? 什么?什么? 快说 怎么回事?
Can you stand it? What? What? What? Come on, what happened?
天啊 麦克 绝对笑死你 我跟你说
Oh, my god, mike. You are gonna die. Listen to this.
这事逗死人了
This is hilarious.
我刚才问汤姆
I just said to tom,
就是 "你愿意做我的竞选伙伴，加入候选人名单吗?"
You know, "Will you join me on the ticket as my running mate?"
好了 告诉他你当时怎么说的
Okay, so then tell what you just did.
又说一遍? 对啊 一定得跟他说
Again? Yeah, definitely tell him.
说吧说吧 等不了了 特别好笑 快告诉他
Please. Can't wait. It's hilarious. Tell him.
好吧 我说 "总统女士 非常遗憾..."
Well, I said, "Madam president, with deep regret..."
不是吧  你真这么说了 他真这么说了
No, you didn't say that. He did not say that.
别着急 等会 高潮还没到呢 接着说
No, wait, that's not even the best part. Listen.
然后我说 "恐怕我--"
Then I said, "I'm afraid--"
"要接受您的邀请了"
"I'm going to have to accept."
他接受了
He accepted.
他接受了 哇哦 太棒了
He accepted. Oh, it's tremendous.
欢迎成为候选人
Welcome to the ticket.
谢谢 麦克 你这个搞笑天王
Thank you, mike. You joker.
好了 你现在要开始运转这事了 对吧?
Okay, you need to go get things going, right?
对了 天 好的 非常遗憾 我得干活了
Oh, gosh, yes. It is with deep regret I must work.
自听到那些熊猫都怀孕后
this is the best announcement
这真是最好的消息了
Since all those pandas got pregnant.
真不知道他说的是什么 干杯!
I don't know what that means. Toast!
非常遗憾 敬非常遗憾
Deep regret. To deep regret.
确实 确实
Indeed, indeed.
好
Yeah.
我们要记住这一刻 不是吗?
Well, we have to mark the moment, don't we?
刚才没拍好  我们往那边移一点吧
I'll tell you what, let's scooch down here just a little bit.
这下好了 可以吧? 开拍
That's good. Yeah? There we go.
快拍 快快快
Take it quick, quick, quick.
行了 就这样吧 够了够了
Okay, all right, that's fine. That's enough.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
现在我是不是该找Amy Brookheimer谈谈
I should sit down with amy brookheimer,
看看需要我做点什么
See where I fit into the plan.
呃 我把她解雇了 对啊 她脑子有点不正常了
Yeah, I had to let her go. Yeah, she went crazy.
这样啊 那你们现在连竞选经理都没有吗?
Yeah. So you don't have a campaign manager?
哦 不不 我们有 肯定的
Oh, no, no. We do, yeah.
一切尽在掌握
That's all completely under control.
我们的竞选经理是...
Our campaign manager is...
kent 收到
Kent. Roger that.
这事儿我都不知道 那就对了
Well, that was a meeting that I wasn't at. That is correct.
媒体对Tom James的回归反响非常热烈
The press are excited about tom james.
那还用说!
I bet they are!
但我们必须尽快公布我们的新竞选经理
But we have to tell them who our new campaign manager is asap.
好的 没问题 你可以去公布了
Okay, good. You can go do that, then.
非常好
That's great.
好的
Okay.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你领带不错  我很喜欢
I love your tie. I love your tie.
太客气了 谢谢
It's so nice. Thank you.
kent 好的
Kent. Yes, ma'am
你那有没有纽约时报?
Do you have "The new york times"?
我给您找一份 没问题 好的
I can get it for you. Absolutely. Good.
她就问我 能不能在她的胸部签名
So she asked me if I would sign her breast.
我告诉她 "还是签在你手臂上吧?"
I said, "How about I sign your arm?"
-Karen  -她说 "那不行 签手臂上谁看啊?"
Karen. She said, "That's no good. Who's gonna see that?"
你现在对我们的团队怎么看?
What do you think about, you know, the group?
我觉得有些人该留
I feel like there are some
有些人该走
people who should be here and some who shouldn't.
总统也是这么想的 哦 那好啊
That's exactly how the president feels. Oh, good.
嗯 所以她授权我 请你离开团队
Yeah, which is why she's asked me to let you go.
真逗 是啊
Interesting. Yeah.
你的香槟里已经下了剧毒的放射性物质
Your champagne's been laced with polonium.
我想说的是 其实没有啦
I mean, not really.
我只是尽量让气氛不那么尴尬而已
It's just to lighten up the moment a little bit.
但是她确实想解雇你
But she definitely wants you to go.
你现在感觉如何?
So how you feeling?
我脑子一片空白
I don't know what to think.
这是难免的 你可以走那边--出去的门在那里
Precisely. You can just use that-- the door right there.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
她走了 总统
all clear, ma'am.
你不必像我一样 冒着生命危险去救人
You don't have to risk your own life to save another like I did
来成为英雄
To join the hero club.
美国人的每一天 都像英雄一样活着
No, every single day americans do something that's heroic.
因为他们相信民主
They live in a democracy.
这才是真正的英雄主义
That's real heroism.
嘿 嘿 嘿 哇哦! 谢谢 谢谢
Hey, hey, hey. Oh! Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你们喜欢刚才的那个吻吗?
Did you guys like that kiss?
喜欢?
You did?
呃 很有意思的是
Well, you know, it's funny
刚才我们的牙齿撞到一起了
because we actually bumped teeth there.
估计你们错过了
I guess you guys missed it,
不过我们有一生的时间来练习
but we have our whole lives to practice that.
我们坚信不疑
And we will.
小心 别碰着这位男士好么?
You leave this man alone, okay?
这可是我们的宝贝
Precious cargo right here.
谢谢 他是我的拉拉队长
Thank you. Well, he's my cheerleader.
我得给他弄点拉拉球来
Yeah, I've got to get him pom-poms.
再次感谢你们的热情
Thank you all so much again.
感谢你 美利坚!
Thank you. America!
是的 谢谢 谢谢
Yes, thank you, thank you.
你这样不累么?
Do you ever get tired of this?
早就累了 对
Really tired of it, yeah.
我在选择Dolye之前审核过的人?
The people that I vetted before I chose doyle?
-候选人确实不少 -对啊 可惜你都看不上眼啊
-There's so many of them. -Yeah, you didn't like any of them.
不过 此一时非彼一时
Well, that was then, and this is not then.
-投票显示Olsen的人气不错 -他有酗酒的前科
-Olsen polled okay. -He's got a drinking problem.
他有酗酒的前科呢
He's got a drinking problem.
是的 他甚至都不肯让别人借用一下鞋油
Yeah, shoe polish and he never even shared.
我们可以挑女性啊 夫人
Well, we could go all female, ma'am.
-什么? -Leanne Harris
-What? -Leanne harris.
你是想要天下大乱吗?
Are you trying to blow up the universe now?
谁想看两个女人捆绑竞选啊?
Who's gonna go for two women on the ticket?
我猜我们还能整天品鲍爽到飞起呢 嗯?
I guess we could all eat pussy all day long, too, right?
Tom James 男性
Tom james is a man.
我们要的是像Tom James这种型的 知道不?
We need a tom jamesy type, you know?
来自南方的拉丁裔
From the south. And latino.
呃 他既不是南方人也不是拉丁裔
Well, he's not southern or latino,
Culverson怎么样?
But what about culverson?
他都86岁了
He's 86.
嗯 这就是为什么不要他的原因 Mike
Yeah, that's why we 86'd him, mike.
候选人得活得过竞选吧
The candidate needs to live up to and through the election.
-那么还是Tom James? -上帝啊 选一个合适的人有这么难吗?
-Tom james? - God, why is it hard to find somebody for this job?
我是说 这是个多么棒的工作啊
I mean, it is such a great job.
极好的工作 嗯
Such a great job. Yeah.
朋友们 我是一个美国能(人)
Folks, I am an ameri-can
我有一个美计划
With a merry plan.
我信奉"吹着口哨上着班"的人生观
I subscribe to a "Whistle while you work" Philosophy.
如果要把这个枪毙掉的话 就别再把他放在中间
If this is supposed to be dead, it shouldn't be in the center.
-夫人 夫人 -很明显
-Ma'am. Ma'am. -There's
我们不可能--
absolutely no way we're going to be able to--
夫人 我也不想祥林嫂一直bb
Ma'am, I don't want to sound like a broken record,
不过我要说 选Tom James Tom James Tom James
But tom james, tom james, tom james.
好好 别吵啦 给老娘安静
Okay,stop it. Just stop it.
为什么不选他?
Why not?
Amy 我可不想你误会
Amy, I don't want you to take this the wrong way,
但你确实有点烦人了
But you are being a little irritating.
嗯 或许不只是一点点吧
Well, maybe not a little bit.
可能是非常 没错
A lot a bit. That's right.
-那你选谁? -我不--
-Then who? -I don't--
他?
Him?
不!不!艹艹艹 别呀!
No! No! Fuck, no!
我说 他完全不合适 好吗?
Well, he's completely inept, right?
但是你们可以化腐朽为神奇 -确实
But you can make inept work. -True.
一个土豆你都能吹上天
You can say the same of a potato.
Ben 去把Pierce给我找来 好吗?
Go get pierce for me, okay, ben?
好 哦...我们要跟他谈谈
Okay. Oh... We should talk to him.
我头痛...
My head hurts...
考虑到有这么多奇妙的可能
From all the wondrous possibilities.
Karen 你觉得Pierce怎么样?
Karen, what do you think of pierce?
要我说 每一个候选人都有优缺点
Well, I think there are pros and cons to every candidate,
所以我们需要权衡他们的优缺点
So we just need to weigh up the pros and cons.
你是不是从未来传送过来
Have you been sent from the future
摧毁我的? 真是效果显著啊
To destroy me? 'cause it's working.
"我觉得每个候选者都有优点和缺点
"I think that each candidate has merits and demerits.
我不知道我的左屁股和右屁股哪个更好
And I don't know my left butt cheek from my right butt cheek,
但是我应该听听两瓣屁股的意见
But I believe in listening to both
来决定要不要从屁眼里放屁"
butt cheeks and then farting out my asshole mouth."
好吧 这连胡话都算不上
Okay. It's not even bullshit.
能说胡话也需要天赋 你毛都没有
Bullshitting takes talent. You have none.
你个只会逼逼的贱人
You are just a blah, blah, blah, blah bitch.
好啦 Amy 够啦
Okay, amy, that is enough.
我一直咬我的舌头来忍着不说话
I have bitten my tongue so long,
都要咬成狗啃的垫子了
It looks like a dog's cushion.
但我再也忍不下去了
But no more.
你把这个工作整得无法进行下去
You have made it impossible to do this job.
你只有两个设置选项--没有决策和烂决策
You have two settings-- no decision and bad decision.
我甚至都不会让你一个人
I wouldn't let you run a bath
在没有海岸警卫队和消防部门
Without having the coast guard
在场的情况下去放洗澡水
And the fire department standing by,
但是你却这样管理美国
But yet here you are running america.
你的出现是这个国家 自有超大桶装食品以来
You are the worst thing that has happened to this country
最大的悲哀
Since food in buckets
也许还要算上奴隶制
And maybe slavery.
我受够你了 我走人
I've had enough. I'm gone.
呃 我想她已经完成了她小小的--
Well, I guess she's finished with her little--
哦 不
Oh, nope.
看啊 她还没说完呢
Look at that, there's more.
-你一事无成 -好吧
-You have achieved nothing.-Uh-huh.
除了一件事
Apart from one thing.
鉴于你是个女的
The fact that you are a woman
我们将来一定不会再有女总统了
means we will have no more women presidents
因为我们尝试过一个女总统 而她绝逼烂透了
Because we tried one and she fucking sucked.
永别 夫人
Good-bye, ma'am.
哎 这个显然都怪我
Well, that was clearly about me.
她是典型的憎恶权威型女性的那种女人
She's just one of those women who resents powerful women.
天哪
Man.
我要和Tom James会面
I'm gonna want to talk to tom james.
-好 -嗯
-Okay. -Yeah.
-Karen -怎么?
-Karen. -Yes?
你怎么看Tom James这个人?
What do you think of tom james?
我怎么看他呀? 我现在是思绪万千呢
What do I think of him? I think there's a lot to think.
-谢谢 -这是我应该的
-Thank you. -Of course.
是202-337--
That's 202-337--
对 我知道Amy的手机号码
Yeah, I know what amy's number is.
只是这次别让我太难堪 好吗?
Just don't make me look too bad in this one, all right?
为什么我要让你难堪?
Why would I make you look bad?
你才是那个会给我穿小鞋的人
You're the one that would make me look bad,
除非你受够了自己的颓废状态
But only after you're done making yourself look bad.
说实话 我认为 你们两个都是了不起的人物 所以...
To be honest, you guys, I think you're both tremendous, so...
妈蛋啊
Holy shit.
Amy辞职了
Amy's gone.
我勒个去 疯了吧
Holy shit, that's insane.
哇哦 我也收到消息了 朋友们
Wow, I'm getting the same thing, guys.
或许我们收到的是一样的短消息呢 哦 是的
Maybe we're getting the same text message. Oh, yeah, we are.
好了 看着 我们得有个计划
Okay, look, we need a plan.
-你们没想法吗? -听起来你早有计划的样子
-Nothing? -It sounded like you had a plan.
你们可是两个人呐
There's two of you.
这就意味着我们一下子就能想出点啥么?
That means we immediately have a fucking plan?
那好 听着 底线是 我们不能让那个傻逼西葫芦
All right, look, bottom line, we cannot let mr. Zucchini
人形蔬菜先生知道这事儿
The human vegetable find out about this.
-我们为什么会告诉他? -我不知道啊!
-Why would we tell him? -I don't know!
听着 闭好你们的嘴就行
Look, just keep your mouths shut.
全都让我来说 知道了吗?
Let me do all the talking, all right?
-Ian -Amy Brookheimer在听电话吗?
-Ian. -Is amy brookheimer on the phone?
我把这个任务交给Jonah了
I'm gonna throw that over to jonah.
通常是他联络Amy 他们有过一段感情
She was his contact. They dated for a while.
-那么 Jonah? -Jonah?
-So, jonah? -Jonah?
谢谢你大爷啊 Dan
Thank you, dan.
呃...
Um...
Amy现在忙于代表大会 抽不出空来
Amy is too busy right now at the convention.
她现在在大会工作
She's working at the convention.
-她在工作哦 -我听说她走人了
-She's working. -I heard she walked.
-哦 我不... -现在我也要走了
-Oh, I hadn't... -which I am going to do now.
不 不 Ian Ian 听我说
No, no, ian, ian. Listen to me.
我有一个小黑本 好吗?
I have a little black book, okay?
我有一些国家安全局都没有的东西
I have numbers the NSA doesn't even know about.
听说过Mike Mcclintock没?
Have you heard of mike mcclintock?
好了 你们两个 出去
Okay, you two, get out of my office.
-幸会 先生 -并不
-It was a pleasure, sir. -No.
-不 握握手 -就不
-Nope. -No.
他演讲前有两到三个演讲者
Two or three speakers before he speaks,
所以我们有大概20分钟
So we have about 20 minutes.
-Tom James!真高兴你回归了 -嘿 Steve
-Tom james! Good to see you back. -Hey, steve.
想我吗? 我也挺想念我自己的
You miss me? I know I missed me.
Mary 沧海桑田
Hey, mary, how come the world changes
为什么你还美丽如初?
And you remain the same?
Cal 听说了你对韩国的评论
Cal, heard what you said about south korea.
我觉得你要说的是朝鲜而非韩国
I think you got the wrong korea.
Marty 爱死你关于侵权法改革的长篇大论
Marty, loving those papers on tort reform.
难怪我的老婆都开始疑神疑鬼了
So hard my wife started to suspect something.
Teresa 你把它扼杀在"摇篮里"了
Teresa, you killed it on "Frontline."
他们得在你演讲完以后把那个桌子设成谋杀现场
They had to put police tape around the desk after you were done.
嘿 Natty 真帅啊你
Hey, natty. What a cool guy.
你菊喷冰晶 尿撒雪花 是吧?
You shit ice cubes and you piss snowflakes, right?
嘿 这大会真棒
Hey. What a great convention.
四年来最棒的
Best one in four years.
-他马上来了 -哦 我的天呐
-He's on his way up. -Oh, my god,
你觉得这是一个好决定吗?
do you think this is the right decision?
-是的 -或许我们应该后退一步 重新商议
-Yes. -Maybe we should take a step back and just reassess.
你在开玩笑吗? 这个家伙可是全美英雄啊
Are you serious? This guy is an all-american hero.
-就像传奇飞车手埃维尔 -对啊
-Like evel knieval. -Yeah.
-不 甚至更好 可爱的Knovley -我喜欢他
-No, better. Lovely knovley. -I like that.
别吹了 Mike 每个人都有不可告人的秘密 随便问哪个贴身秘书都知道
Come on, mike, everyone has skeletons. Ask any bag man.
-这个人不一样 不一样 -他有一个秘密 她就在你面前
-Not this guy. No. -He has one skeleton. You're looking at her.
-哦 我的天 这就是你不想选他的原因吗? -嗯哪
Oh, my god, is that why you didn't want to chose him? Mm-hmm.
-好啦 夫人 该你出场了 -好的
-Okay, ma'am, show time. -Okay.
-客房服务 -哦 老天!
-Room service. -Oh, god!
哦 你来了呀 Tom James
oh, come on, tom james.
我身着闪亮盔甲的骑士啊
My knight in shining armor.
我的藏在总统女士身体里的小少女
My damsel in-- madam president.
Mike Mcclintock你认识吧
You know mike mcclintock.
-Mike 你好吗? -参议员
-Mike, how are you? -Senator.
-这是Kent Davison -参议员 幸会
-And kent davison. -Senator, a pleasure.
-幸会 幸会 -我是Karen
-It's good to see you. -I'm karen.
-Gary -你想要来点什么喝的吗?
-Gary. -So can we offer you something to drink?
我可以大杀四方扒皮饮血
I could murder and make a lampshade out of a manhattan.
不过来一杯水就好--谢谢
but just a water will be-- thank you.
-嗯嗯 那当然 很好 -呃 不好意思
-Uh-huh. Absolutely. Great. -Um, excuse me.
我也想来点喝的
I would like something to drink.
-呃 水? -我要波本酒 纯的
-Uh-huh. Water? -Bourbon, neat.
啊 好的
Yeah, okay.
你得先到我的房间去
You need to go straighten up my room.
-好的 -快点 -你好啊
-Okay. -Hurry up. -Hello.
那我们就往这边走吧...来来来?
So why don't we just head this way... This way?
...以便有更多私人闲聊时间 -好的
...So we can have a little private gabbing time. -Sure.
聊天时间 聊天时间
Gabbing time. Gabbing time.
-对不起 -没事
-Excusez-moi. -That's all right.
没事儿没事儿 来吧
It's fine. Come.
你又回归政坛了呢 嗯?
So you're back in the game, huh?
-的确是 -真棒
-I certainly am. -Wonderful.
-你感觉怎么样啊? -很好 不错
-How are you feeling? -Good. Feels good.
你的儿子Ryan怎么样了?他最近好吗?
And what about your son ryan? How is he doing?
他在好转中 他承受了太多痛苦
He's on the mend. He's in a lot of pain.
-嗯 -他们在他的髋骨打了些钉子
-Mmm. -They inserted these pins into his hip.
得花挺长时间来治愈吧
And it's gonna be a long road.
我不想打断你 但我必须要问你一些事儿 Tom
I don't want to rush you, but I do need to ask you this, tom.
你愿意作为我的竞选伙伴
Would you join me
参与竞选么?
On the ticket as my running mate?
总统女士 我--
Madam president, I--
我对于这件事儿得犹豫一下
I had a feeling that this was in the wind.
那是 好吧 嗯嗯
Sure, okay. Yeah.
恐怕我 深感抱歉...
I'm afraid, with deep regret...
哦 我的天
Oh, my god.
...我得接受你的邀请
...That I'm going to have to accept.
等等 什么?
Wait, what?
不 你怎么能这么耍我啊!
No, you didn't just do that to me!
我...我...
i... I...
哦 天哪 伙计们!伙计们!
Oh, my god. Guys! Guys!
伙计们 看我得到了什么!看看我得到了什么!
Guys, look what I got! Look what I got!
-好消息啊 -我拉他入伙啦
-Sounds like good news. -I got him.
-欢迎来到我们团队 参议员 谢谢 谢谢
-Welcome aboard, senator. Thank you. Thank you.
你太坏了 你个小淘气啊
You are so bad. You are naughty.
我刚刚说"你愿意
I just said, "Would you
作为我的竞选伙伴参与竞选么?"
join me on the ticket as my running mate?"
- 这不是很玄乎吗? - 一点都不觉得
- Isn't that spooky? - Not even remotely.
好啦 去把Danny Chung找来 Mike! 哦 我的天!
Okay, go get danny chung. Mike! Oh, my god!
啊 他们发现那个死囚还有脉搏呐
Ah, they found a pulse on the death row guy.
哦 现在他们可以名正言顺地杀他了
Oh. Now they can kill him properly.
天哪 你觉得他们能干好吧
God, you'd think they could do that right.
死囚牢房(死成串)--线索就在名称里
Death row-- the clue is in the name.
欢迎来到真实的华府 孩子们
Welcome to the real dc, boys.
Dan中心
Dan central.
先生们 你们好 我是Sidney Purcell
Hello, gentlemen. Sidney purcell.
-嗨 Jonah Ryan -哦 Jonah
-Hi, jonah ryan. -Oh, jonah.
很好 Dan 去给客人倒点咖啡好吗?
Excellent. Dan, why don't you get these guys some coffee?
哦 不 不用给我倒咖啡
Oh, no, you don't need to get me a coffee.
虽然 咖啡确实听起来不错
Although, coffee actually does sound delicious.
啊 有趣的是 咖啡机正好坏了
Yeah, funny thing. I think the machine's on the fritz.
是吗? 我们刚刚才喝过呀
Is it? We had coffee earlier.
不可能就坏了吧
There's no way it could be on the fritz.
再去检查下嘛 看看是不是这样
Just double check and see if it is.
如果没坏 我要一杯豆奶卡布奇诺
But if it's not, I think I'll take a soy cap.
-Richard你要啥? 应个景 蛋奶拿铁不错
And, richard? Eggnog latte if it's in season.
是吗? 不 不是吧 好了 我要一杯低脂卡布奇诺
Is it? No, it isn't. Okay, I'll have a skinny cap.
如果有意大利脆饼干就更棒啦
And a biscotti if you've got it.
那我要一杯双份浓缩咖啡
And I'll have a double espresso.
-一会儿见 伙计们 -完美了
-I'll see you guys in a minute. -Fantastic.
哦 Dan 真好喝呐
Oh, dan, that's good.
我们的研究方向是杀虫的手段
So we're interested in finding the pesticide levers.
尤其对那些对杀虫剂提议起到推动作用的人
Specifically the levers that make pesticides happen.
而这位Jonah就是幕后操盘手 是不是呀?
And jonah here is the guy behind the guy. Isn't that right?
是的 啊 命运之轮润滑者
Yeah, oh, I'm the wheel-greaser.
暗线操纵大师 江湖上都是我的传奇
I'm the puppet master. A man of many nicknames.
辣妹杀手
Poon slayer.
玩线上游戏的时候 电子游戏晓得不啦?
When I'm online. Video games?
副总统不参选了
The vice president is leaving the ticket.
是吗 等等 什么?
Yep. Wait, what?
副总统不参选了?
The vice president is leaving the ticket?
四-是的 嗯
Y-yes. Yes, he is.
我怎么会和你同时听到这个消息?
How am I hearing this at the same time as you?
呃 重要的是我们有后备计划
Well, the important thing is that we have a plan b.
是吧 Dan?
Right, dan?
是呀 呃...
Yes. Uh...
我给我的好伙伴Amy Brookheimer打电话
I'm gonna call my good friend amy brookheimer.
她是总统的竞选经理
She's the president's campaign manager.
我和她亲密得来比两个胖子挤电梯还亲密
She and I are closer than two fat guys in an elevator.
- 这没什么大不了的 - 那什么? 你别操心啦
-This is not a big deal. -You know what? Building off that,
我也要给Amy打电话
I'm actually gonna go ahead and give her a call, too.
我们以前还约过会呐 我对她知根知底
We used to date, so I know her inside and out.
我以前给Ames干活 实际上 我亲昵地简称她为Ames--
I used to work for ames. In fact, I call her ames for short--
等等 实际上 Amy更像简称
Wait, actually, it's long for amy.
好吧 打通电话后告诉我
Okay, let me know when you have her.
好
Right.
我上辈子造了什么孽才摊上Karen这货?
What did I do in a past life to deserve karen?
你上辈子下指令偷袭珍珠港
I think you must have given the go-ahead for pearl harbor.
呃 Karen问题吧
Well, the problem with karen
她是总统最好的朋友
is that she's the president's best friend.
说实话 是最好的女性朋友
Best female friend, let's be honest.
好好 小伙伴们 Chung随时都会来
Okay, everybody, chung should be here any second.
- 很好 - 我刚才听到Chung随时都会到来
-All right. -I just heard chung should be here any second.
我们有个会要开 我说得对吗?
We've got ourselves a meeting. Am I right?
你说得对 去摆平他们吧 夫人
You are right. Go get 'em, ma'am.
别表现得太积极了 男人们不喜欢那样
Don't look desperate. Men don't like that.
我第一次在这儿演说
The first time I spoke here,
- 他们叫它Chung狂热 - 我记忆深刻
-They called it chungmania. -I do remember that.
-Chung狂热 -当然
-Chungmania. -Of course.
我记得我当时是如此激动 因为有一个"狂热"作为后缀
And I remember being so excited to have a mania named after me.
-那是当然 -我引领了Chung狂热热潮
-Sure. -I had chungmania mania.
我喜欢你讲的这个故事 太有趣啦
I love it when you tell that story. It's so funny.
那啥 Danny 一月份来吧
Well, danny, come January,
我会感到非常荣幸
I would be so pleased
如果你能来我身边辅佐我
If you would serve alongside me
当我的副总统
As my vice president.
总统女士 你给我了一个莫大的荣誉
You do me a great honor, madam president.
-是呀 是呀 -但是我得和我老婆商量商量
-Yeah. Yeah. -But I do need to consult my wife.
哦 那当然 哦 不 不 不 是的
Oh, of course. Oh, no, no, no, yes.
还有我的圣经 虽然她也是我的圣经 所以我有两个圣经
And my bible. Although she is my bible, so that's two bibles.
嗯 在这15分钟里 你花多长时间
Well, you take as many of the 15 minutes available
来做决定都行
As you need to make this decision.
行 谢谢 谢谢你
Sure. Thank you. Thank you.
Pierce众议员
Congressman pierce.
我听说你们在找一个新的副总统
I hear you guys are looking for a new vice president.
-不可能是你 -不
-It's not gonna be you. -No,
我只是想祝你们好运
I just wanted to wish you guys good luck.
哦 真好啊 滚开吧 老子很忙
Oh, that's nice. Fuck off, I'm busy.
副总统Doyle退出竞选
Vice president doyle stepping off the ticket.
谁做的决定?
Who made this decision?
这个共同决策是由总统 副总统
It was a joint decision made by the president,
以及副总统的
Vice president, and the vice president's,
呃...前列腺医生决定的
Uh... Prostate doctor.
当了30年的参议员
30 years as a senator
感觉你屁眼上镜的时间比你脸还多
And your asshole's getting more screen time than your face.
我知道你一直对Jonah Ryan有性趣
I understand you've been feeling up jonah ryan.
说到有性趣 我指一直以来都性致高昂
And by up, I mean all the way up.
Furlong议员可不想听这些
Congressman furlong does not want to hear this.
哦 我他妈的特别真心喜爱听
Oh, which means I absolutely, totally fucking do.
-请继续 -我知道你玩弄了Jonah的蛋蛋
-Please go on. -I understand you've been twirling jonah's balls
就像是某种减压神器似的
Like they're some kind of exotic stress reducer.
我也希望有人能性侵我的小弟
I wish someone would sexually assault my staff.
而我的小弟是指我的小弟弟
And by staff I mean penis.
-哦 你们是在开玩笑吗 -不 听着
-Oh, you guys are serious. -No, listen.
我是说 我们哪个没有玩过某个家伙来爽一爽?
I mean, which of us hasn't gotten off in some guy's junk?
-你知道 开玩笑而已嘛? -我就没有
-You know, just for a laugh? -I haven't.
我要你拿你的脏手 把你的桌子清理干净
I want you to use your dirty hands, clean out your desk.
-你被开除啦 -你--
-You're fired. -You--
先生 我做的每件事 每件事
Sir, everything I have done, everything...
都是为了效忠您
has been to serve you.
玩弄Jonah更是忠上加忠
And that goes double for fondling Jonah.
你看了吗 这真是个很吸引人的节目啊
Have you been watching this? This is a fascinating show.
我知道 这个问题和前列腺都很大
I know that it's big, the problem and the prostate,
不是件好事
which is not good.
听着就像你要死了一样
Sounds like you might die.
- 总统女士 - 我的好伙伴来了
- Madam President. - Here's my guy.
- 我们开始吧 - 我们开始吧
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
你和你的两部圣经都谈过了 对吧
You talk with both of your Bibles, did you?
- 是的 谈过了 呃 - 好啊 过来 过来 过来
- I have, and, um... - Yes, come, come, come, come.
- 我非常愿意作为副总统来辅佐您 - 哦 天啊
- I would love to serve you as vice president... - Oh, my God.
- 但是我不能这么做 - 什么？
- But I can't. - Hmm?
我不能
I can't.
你在说笑吗? 你怎么能拒绝这样的好事?
Are you kidding? How could you possibly say no to this?
- 可以不要拍了吗? - 可以不要拍了吗!
- Could you please stop? - Could you please stop?!
谢谢 呃
Thank you. Um...
我只能说 是因为家庭原因
all I can say is it's family issues.
怎么 你肚子被搞大了? 到底是什么原因?
What, are you knocked up? What's the real reason?
- 什么原因? - 是您行事的方式 女士
- What is it? - It's the way you operate, ma'am.
您有很棒的行事方式
You have a great way of operating.
- 我当然有了 - 非常棒 真的
- I absolutely do. - It's terrific, really.
- 当然了 - 不过不是我喜欢的行事方式
- Yeah. - But it's not the way I like to operate.
所以 很抱歉 我真的不可以
So, I'm sorry, I just can't.
- 我能看出来您不高兴 - 没有 我 我是说 我是不高兴
- I can see you're upset. - No, I'm not... I mean, I am upset.
我怎么可能高兴? 这简直是胡闹
Why wouldn't I be upset? This is bullshit.
我可以向您保证 没有人比我更难过了
Well, I can assure you there is no one more upset than me.
你看起来一点都不难过 Danny
You don't look upset at all, Danny.
这军队里的训练的好
That's just military training.
很抱歉 我还得去大会上发言
I'm sorry, but I have to address the convention.
不 等一下 等一下 等等
No, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait, wait.
对不起 不是故意拉你的 不过听我说
I'm sorry, didn't mean to pull that. But listen to me.
- 做了副总统后接着是什么? - 总统
- What comes after veep? - President?
总统 对啊
President, right.
而且说不定 某一天莫个人可能就
And you never know. Someday somebody might just...
再次表示抱歉 谢谢您能问我
I'm sorry. Again, thank you for asking.
我很荣幸 也很惭愧
I am honored and humbled.
你根本没有!
No, you're not!
- 他拒绝了 - 哦 天啊
- He said no. - Oh, God!
事实上 我再详尽地说一遍
Actually, let me elaborate on that.
那个狗屎般的两面派的肥傻逼拒绝了
The shitty, two-faced, fat fucking turd said no.
好吧 这是个意外 我们需要面对
Okay, this is a curveball we will need to address.
我得宣布一个人选啊 我该怎么办?
I've got to announce someone. What am I supposed to do?
要我走上讲台
I'm supposed to walk out on stage
然后一直走直到我从另一边掉下去吗?
and then keep walking till I fall off the otheside?
我的建议是Tom James
My advice... Tom James.
所有人都喜欢Tom James
Everyone likes Tom James.
连我都喜欢Tom James 我讨厌所有人
I like Tom James and I hate everyone.
他有一个残疾儿子 打勾
He has a disabled son, check.
为了国家负过伤 打勾
Wounded serving his country, check.
这个清单勾打完了吗? 是的
Is the checklist complete? Yeah.
- 不行 - 我们俩都不同意
- No. - We both say no.
- 我有个主意 - 不 你没有 你只是觉得你有
- I got an idea. - No, you don't. You just think you do.
说吧 Gary 你肯定想出来什么了
Go on, Gary. think you've got something.
谢谢你 Karen 我们为什么不把Doyal请回来呢?
Thank you, Karen. Why don't we ask Doyle back?
他已经宣布要走了
He announced he's leaving.
好吧 有人想喝咖啡吗?
Okay, does anybody want a coffee?
Maddox! 对啊 Maddox
Maddox! That's right, Maddox.
- 少数族裔 参过军 - 哦 就是他了
- Minority, military. - Oh, that's your veep.
所有人都不许再有其他想法了
Everybody stop having ideas.
- 你在开玩笑吧 - 没有 我一点都没有
- You're kidding. - No, I'm not kidding at all.
Mike 去叫Maddox 联系他的团队
Mike, get Maddox. Find his team.
- 收到 现在就去 - 女士 那个死刑犯的最新消息
- On it. I'm on it. - Ma'am, update on the death row guy.
Sue 别再提他了 他根本就不重要
Sue, forget him. He's irrelevant.
- 他死了 - 哦 终于死了 不是吗？
- He died. - Oh, finally, right?
又少了件让人担心的事了
It's one less thing to worry about.
你在哪 你现在赶紧来
Where are you? I need you to go
会议大厅这层 Todd 让Maddox过来
to the convention floor, Todd, and get Maddox.
嘿 Mike 我听说你们在找新的副总统
Hey, Mike, I hear you guys are looking for a new veep.
- 呃 不会是你的 - 哦 不 不 不 天啊
- Uh, it won't be you. - Oh, no, no, no, God.
我只是想推荐一个人 哦 天啊
I was just gonna suggest someone... oh, God.
我是想说Danny Chung可以
I was gonna suggest Danny Chung.
很明显 他是最好的选择
He seems like the obvious choice.
他很适合竞选 他的身材也很好
He's fit to run. He's so physically fit.
非常感谢你们给我这么热情的欢迎
Thank you so much for this warmest of welcomes.
这让我想起了我第一次到这时的情景
You know, it reminds me of the first time I was here.
Chung狂热
Chungmania.
我怎么会忘了这件事呢？
How will I ever live that down, huh?
好吧 你肯定知道
Well, of course you know
我今天和你谈话的目的 George
why I asked to speak with you today, George.
我想着肯定不是找我要汉堡包秘方的
Well, I imagine it's not for my hamburger recipe.
- 很好吃吗？ - 我不做饭的
- Is it good? - Well, I don't cook.
- 我开玩笑的 - 是啊 当然 当然
- That was a joke. - Right, sure, sure.
事实上 我的味觉不是很灵敏（品位低）
Actually, I have very little sense of taste.
所以选了这条领带
Hence the tie.
好的 很好 很好
Okay. Great. Great.
好吧 我真的很想知道你对于
Well, I really wanted to know how you might feel
做我的竞选伙伴是怎么想的
about being my running mate.
好啊
Great.
我是说 我的下属们告诉我我应该多开开玩笑
I mean, my people told me I should joke around.
- 嗯 是啊 - 不过我是个有着强烈野心的人
- Uh-huh, yeah. - But I'm a fiercely ambitious man.
而且我知道怎么把事情做好
And I know how to get things done.
并不是说你不行 只是人们都说你不行
Not that you don't. Though people say you don't.
好的
Okay.
我们在考虑所有选择
Well, we're looking at all options.
哦 Ben叫我呢
Oh, Ben is calling me.
所以我得去 他刚把门关上了
So I've got to... He just closed the door,
我得过去了
so I'm gonna have to head out.
非常感谢你
But thank you so much.
感谢你能过来 嗯
I appreciate you coming by, yeah.
等一下 你是说这些都是
Wait a minute, you're telling me that these are all